[{
	"question": "What year was the first Iron Man movie was released?",
	"options": [
		"A. 2005", 
		"B. 2008", 
		"C. 2010", 
		"D. 2012"],
	"answer": "B. 2008"
},
{
	"question": "What is the name of the thor's hammer?",
	"options": [
		"A. Vanir", 
		"B. Mjolnir",
		"C. Aesir", 
		"D. Norn"],
	"answer": "B. Mjolnir"
},
{
	"question": "What is Captain America's sheild made of?",
	"options": [
		"A. Adamantanium", 
		"B. Vibranium", 
		"C. Promethium", 
		"D. Carbodanium"],
	"answer": "B. Vibranium"
},
{
	"question": "Where is Superman's home?",
	"options": [
		"A. Galactus", 
		"B. Gotham", 
		"C. Metropolis", 
		"D. Krypton"],
	"answer": "D. Krypton"
},
{
	"question": "What is the Superman's true name?",
	"options": [
		"A. Bruce Wayne", 
		"B. Clark Kent", 
		"C. Kal-El", 
		"D. Lex luthor"],
	"answer": "C. Kal-El"
},
{
	"question": "What is the true name of the Batgirl?",
	"options": ["A. Barbara Gordon", 
		"B. Lois Lane", 
		"C. Barry Hardy", 
		"D. Haevey Dent"],
	"answer": "A. Barbara Gordon"
},
{
	"question": "In Marvel, How many infinity stones are there?",
	"options": [
		"A. 9", 
		"B. 6", 
		"C. 7", 
		"D. 5"],
	"answer": "B. 6"
},
{
	"question": "Who managed to punch superman into a space coma?",
	"options": [
		"A. Booster Gold", 
		"B. Doomsday", 
		"C. Lex Luthor", 
		"D. Darkseid"],
	"answer": "B. Doomsday"
},
{
	"question": "What is the real name of the Black Panther?",
	"options": [
		"A. T'Challa", 
		"B. M'Baku", 
		"C. N'Jadaka", 
		"D. N'Jobu"],
	"answer": "A. T'Challa"
},
{
	"question": "Who played Christopher Nolan's Joker?",
	"options": [
		"A. Jared Leto", 
		"B. Jck Nicholson", 
		"C. Caesar Romeo", 
		"D. Heath Ledger"],
	"answer": "D. Heath Ledger"
},
{
	"question": "WHo was the last Holder of the Space Stone before Thanos claims it for his infinity gauntlet?",
	"options": [
		"A. Thor", 
		"B. Loki", 
		"C. The collector", 
		"D. Tony stark"],
	"answer": "B. Loki"
},
{
	"question": "Who does the Mad Titan sacrifice to the acquire the Soul Stone?",
	"options": [
		"A. Ebony Maw", 
		"B. Gamora", 
		"C. Nebula", 
		"D. Cull Obsidian"],
	"answer": "B. Gamora"
},
{
	"question": "What is the true identity of the Green Latern we know best?",
	"options": [
            "A. Hal Jordon", 
		"B. Barry Allen", 
		"C. Kal-El", 
		"D. Joe-El"],
	"answer": "A. Hal Jordon"
},
{
	"question": "What is the Superman logo a Kryptonian symbol for?",
	"options": [
            "A. Power", 
		"B. Aliens", 
		"C. Hope", 
		"D. Beauty"],
	"answer": "C. Hope"
},
{
	"question": "Who is killed by Loki in Avengers?",
	"options": ["A. Maria Hill",
		"B. Agent Coulson",
		"C. Nick Fury",
		"D. Doctor Erik Selvig"],
	"answer": "B. Agent Coulson"
},
{
	"question": "In DC, Which superhero has supertools such as Magic lasso and bullet proof bracelets",
	"options": ["A. Cat woman",
		"B. Wonder Woman",
		"C. Grren Latern",
		"D. Super Girl"],
	"answer": "B. Wonder Woman"
},
{
	"question": "Sharon Carter is whose great-niece?",
	"options": ["A. Captain America",
		"B. Peggy Carter",
		"C. Nick Fury",
		"D. Tony Stark"],
	"answer": "B. Peggy Carter"
},
{
	"question": "Who was responsible for Kinf T'Chaka's death?",
	"options": ["A. Loki",
		"B. Winetr Soldier",
		"C. Zemo",
		"D. Captain America"],
	"answer": "C. Zemo"
},
{
	"question": "Who was the first female superhero of the Juctice Society of America?",
	"options": [
            "A. Storm",
		"B. Wonder Woman",
		"C. Elecktra",
		"D. Cat Woman"],
	"answer": "B. Wonder Woman"
},
{
	"question": "Barbara Gordon, the father of Batgirl, is the ___________ of the Gotham City?",
	"options": ["A. Mayor",
		"B. Governer",
		"C. Normal Man",
		"D. The police cheif"],
	"answer": "D. The police cheif"
},
{
	"question": "The Green Latern gains his power from the which object?",
	"options": ["A. Glasses",
		"B. Necklace",
		"C. Ring",
		"D. Suite"],
	"answer": "C. Ring"
},
{
	"question": "Who was the winter soldier?",
	"options": ["A. Bucky",
		"B. Luke",
		"C. Steve Rodger",
		"D. Tony Stark"],
	"answer": "A. Bucky"
},
{
	"question": "Thor's Mjolnir is made from the metal of dying _________?",
	"options": ["A. Celestial",
		"B. Sun",
		"C. Star",
		"D. Lightning"],
	"answer": "C. Star"
},
{
	"question": "Wonder Woman come from which island?",
	"options": ["A. The sun island",
		"B. The eden isle",
		"C. The emerald island",
		"D. The paradise island"],
	"answer": "D. The paradise island"
},
{
	"question": "Which newspaper does Spidermn-Peter Parker- work for?",
	"options": [
            "A. The daily bugle",
		"B. The daily planet",
		"C. The daily gothamite",
		"D. The daily news"],
	"answer": "A. The daily bugle"
},
{
	"question": "Ehat are the claws of the wolverine made of?",
	"options": [
            "A. Adamantium",
		"B. Titanium",
		"C. Vibranuim",
		"D. Cadmium"],
	"answer": "A. Adamantium"
},
{
	"question": "With the special memory fibre in his cape,Batman is able to.......?",
	"options": ["A. Communicate with Batmobile",
		"B. Slowly fall",
		"C. Disappear",
		"D. Voice change"],
	"answer": "B. Slowly fall"
},
{
	"question": "Pepper Potts is allergic to what?" ,
	"options": [
            "A. Apple",
		"B. Strawberries",
		"C. Mango",
		"D. Banana"],
	"answer": "B. Strawberries"
}]
